[
    {
        "text": "Elon Musk founded SpaceX in 2002.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 18,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tesla is headquartered in Palo Alto, California.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 37,
                "end": 47,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jeff Bezos is the founder of Amazon.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 29,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Microsoft was founded by Bill Gates in 1975.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 39,
                "end": 43,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Apple is located in Cupertino.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mark Zuckerberg created Facebook in 2004.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 36,
                "end": 40,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Google was founded in Mountain View.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Larry Page and Sergey Brin founded Google.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 15,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 35,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Satya Nadella is the CEO of Microsoft.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tim Cook leads Apple from California.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 15,
                "end": 20,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "OpenAI developed ChatGPT in 2022.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 17,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "developed"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sam Altman is CEO of OpenAI in San Francisco.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "NVIDIA is based in Santa Clara.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jensen Huang founded NVIDIA in 1993.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meta is headquartered in Menlo Park.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sundar Pichai is CEO of Google.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Netflix was founded in 1997 in California.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "date"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founded_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Reed Hastings founded Netflix.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Anthropic created Claude in 2023.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 18,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "developed"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dario Amodei is CEO of Anthropic.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Twitter was founded by Jack Dorsey.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "person"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jack Dorsey also founded Square.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Alibaba was founded by Jack Ma in China.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 34,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tencent is headquartered in Shenzhen.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Pony Ma founded Tencent in 1998.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 16,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Samsung is based in Seoul, South Korea.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 25,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 38,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sony was founded in Tokyo in 1946.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 25,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 29,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Toyota is headquartered in Japan.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "BMW is a German automotive company.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 3,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 9,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Volkswagen was founded in 1937 in Germany.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "date"
            },
            {
                "start": 34,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founded_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "SpaceX launched Falcon 9 in 2010.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 16,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "developed"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tesla released Model 3 in 2017.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 15,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "developed"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Apple launched iPhone in 2007.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 15,
                "end": 21,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "developed"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Google developed Android operating system.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 17,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "product"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Microsoft created Windows in 1985.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 18,
                "end": 25,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 29,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "developed"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Guido van Rossum created Python.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "programlang"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "James Gosling invented Java at Sun Microsystems.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 47,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Bjarne Stroustrup created C++ in 1983.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 18,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 34,
                "end": 38,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "creator_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dennis Ritchie created C language.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 14,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "programlang"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Linus Torvalds created Linux in 1991.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 14,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 28,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 32,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "creator_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Brendan Eich invented JavaScript.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "programlang"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Anders Hejlsberg created TypeScript at Microsoft.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 39,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Yann LeCun is AI researcher at Meta.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": []
    },
    {
        "text": "Geoffrey Hinton worked at Google.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": []
    },
    {
        "text": "DeepMind is located in London.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Demis Hassabis founded DeepMind.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "IBM is headquartered in New York.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 3,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Oracle was founded in 1977 by Larry Ellison.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "date"
            },
            {
                "start": 30,
                "end": 43,
                "label": "person"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founded_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 2,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Salesforce is based in San Francisco.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Marc Benioff founded Salesforce in 1999.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 35,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Uber was founded in San Francisco in 2009.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 37,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Travis Kalanick co-founded Uber.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Airbnb is headquartered in San Francisco.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 40,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Brian Chesky founded Airbnb in 2008.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Spotify was founded in Stockholm in 2006.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 36,
                "end": 40,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Daniel Ek founded Spotify.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 18,
                "end": 25,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Stripe is based in San Francisco.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 19,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Patrick Collison founded Stripe in 2010.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 16,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 35,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Shopify is headquartered in Ottawa.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tobias Lutke founded Shopify in 2006.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 28,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 32,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Zoom was founded by Eric Yuan in 2011.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 33,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Slack was acquired by Salesforce.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": []
    },
    {
        "text": "Stewart Butterfield founded Slack.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 19,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dropbox is based in San Francisco.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Drew Houston founded Dropbox in 2007.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Reddit was founded in 2005.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Steve Huffman co-founded Reddit.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Pinterest is headquartered in San Francisco.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 30,
                "end": 43,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ben Silbermann founded Pinterest.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 14,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "LinkedIn was founded by Reid Hoffman in 2002.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 40,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Snapchat was created by Evan Spiegel.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "person"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "TikTok is owned by ByteDance.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 19,
                "end": 28,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": []
    },
    {
        "text": "Zhang Yiming founded ByteDance in Beijing.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 34,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Huawei is based in Shenzhen, China.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 19,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 29,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ren Zhengfei founded Huawei in 1987.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Baidu is headquartered in Beijing.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Robin Li founded Baidu in 2000.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 17,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Xiaomi was founded in Beijing in 2010.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 33,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lei Jun founded Xiaomi.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 16,
                "end": 22,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "JD.com is based in Beijing.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 19,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Richard Liu founded JD.com in 1998.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 30,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Meituan is headquartered in Beijing.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Wang Xing founded Meituan in 2010.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 18,
                "end": 25,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 29,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Nvidia developed CUDA platform.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 17,
                "end": 21,
                "label": "product"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "AMD is based in Santa Clara.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 3,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 16,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Lisa Su is CEO of AMD.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 18,
                "end": 21,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Intel is headquartered in Santa Clara.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Pat Gelsinger is CEO of Intel.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Qualcomm is based in San Diego.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Palantir is headquartered in Denver.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 29,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Peter Thiel co-founded Palantir.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Databricks is based in San Francisco.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ali Ghodsi is CEO of Databricks.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Snowflake is headquartered in Bozeman.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 30,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The iPhone was first released in 2007 by Apple.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 4,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 33,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "date"
            },
            {
                "start": 41,
                "end": 46,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 2,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Samsung Galaxy is a popular smartphone series.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 14,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "MacBook Pro was developed by Apple engineers.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 29,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The PlayStation 5 was released in November 2020.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 4,
                "end": 17,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 34,
                "end": 47,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Nintendo Switch became popular in 2017.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 34,
                "end": 38,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Xbox Series X was developed by Microsoft.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 40,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The Model S is made by Tesla.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 4,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 29,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "AirPods Pro were introduced by Apple in 2019.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 40,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Surface Pro is a product line from Microsoft.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 35,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The Pixel phone was created by Google.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 4,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Python was created by Guido van Rossum in 1991.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 38,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 42,
                "end": 46,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Java was developed by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 39,
                "end": 55,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Rust was first released in 2010 by Mozilla.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "date"
            },
            {
                "start": 35,
                "end": 42,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 2,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Go programming language was created by Google.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 2,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 39,
                "end": 45,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Swift is developed by Apple for iOS.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 27,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 32,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "product"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Kotlin was created by JetBrains.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "C++ was developed by Bjarne Stroustrup at Bell Labs.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 3,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 43,
                "end": 52,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Ruby was created by Yukihiro Matsumoto in Japan.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 43,
                "end": 48,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "PHP was originally developed by Rasmus Lerdorf in 1994.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 3,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 32,
                "end": 46,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 50,
                "end": 54,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "R programming language was released in 1995.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 1,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 39,
                "end": 43,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Google was incorporated on September 4, 1998.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Facebook launched in February 2004.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Amazon was founded on July 5, 1994 in Seattle.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 34,
                "label": "date"
            },
            {
                "start": 38,
                "end": 45,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founded_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Twitter was launched on March 21, 2006.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 38,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Netflix started in August 1997.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tim Cook is the CEO of Apple Inc.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 23,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sundar Pichai leads Google as CEO.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Andy Jassy became CEO of Amazon in 2021.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 35,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jensen Huang is the CEO of NVIDIA.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sam Altman leads OpenAI as CEO.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 17,
                "end": 23,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Dara Khosrowshahi is the CEO of Uber.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 17,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 32,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Reed Hastings co-founded Netflix.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 13,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "BMW is headquartered in Munich, Germany.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 3,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 32,
                "end": 39,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Toyota is based in Toyota City, Japan.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 32,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Samsung headquarters is in Seoul, South Korea.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 34,
                "end": 45,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Alibaba is located in Hangzhou, China.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "location"
            },
            {
                "start": 32,
                "end": 37,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tencent is based in Shenzhen.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 20,
                "end": 28,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    }
]