[
    {
        "text": "Elon Musk founded SpaceX in 2002.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 18,
                "end": 24,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 28,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tesla was founded by Elon Musk in California.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 21,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 34,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jeff Bezos is the CEO of Amazon.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Apple Inc. was founded by Steve Jobs in Cupertino.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 40,
                "end": 49,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Microsoft was founded by Bill Gates in 1975.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 9,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 35,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 39,
                "end": 43,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Google is headquartered in Mountain View, California.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 52,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Mark Zuckerberg created Facebook in 2004.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 15,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 24,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 36,
                "end": 40,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founded_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Tim Cook is the current CEO of Apple.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 8,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 31,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Sundar Pichai leads Google as its CEO.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 19,
                "end": 25,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "OpenAI was founded by Sam Altman in San Francisco.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 36,
                "end": 49,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "ChatGPT was developed by OpenAI.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 7,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 25,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Python was created by Guido van Rossum.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "programlang"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 38,
                "label": "person"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "creator_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Nvidia is based in Santa Clara.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 19,
                "end": 30,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Jensen Huang is the CEO of Nvidia.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 11,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 33,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "The iPhone was invented by Apple in 2007.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 4,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 32,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 36,
                "end": 40,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "released_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Larry Page and Sergey Brin founded Google.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 10,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 15,
                "end": 26,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 35,
                "end": 41,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "founder_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Amazon was established by Jeff Bezos in Seattle.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 6,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 26,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 40,
                "end": 47,
                "label": "location"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "founder_of"
            },
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 2,
                "label": "located_in"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "Satya Nadella became CEO of Microsoft in 2014.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 12,
                "label": "person"
            },
            {
                "start": 27,
                "end": 36,
                "label": "organisation"
            },
            {
                "start": 40,
                "end": 44,
                "label": "date"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 0,
                "tail": 1,
                "label": "ceo_of"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "BERT was developed by Google AI.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 4,
                "label": "algorithm"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 31,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "text": "GPT-4 is a product of OpenAI.",
        "entities": [
            {
                "start": 0,
                "end": 5,
                "label": "product"
            },
            {
                "start": 22,
                "end": 28,
                "label": "organisation"
            }
        ],
        "relations": [
            {
                "head": 1,
                "tail": 0,
                "label": "developed"
            }
        ]
    }
]